<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0ldMate's Page</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on 0ldMate's Page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>
Who Am I? My name is Josh, however I often go by the name 0ldMate. I&amp;rsquo;m a hacker, climber and a mechanical keyboard enthusiast.
What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with the site? It&amp;rsquo;s basically just a place for me to share some of my knowledge/passions. I hope you get something out of it.
Where can I find you? Github - https://github.com/0ldMate
Twitter - @0ldMate_</description></item><item><title>Elastic Stack - How you can use it to assist your Incident Response</title><link>/posts/tech/elastic-stack-how-you-can-use-it-to-assist-your-in-f31f7a3f9a8a42c0b860523f4b79cc68/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/tech/elastic-stack-how-you-can-use-it-to-assist-your-in-f31f7a3f9a8a42c0b860523f4b79cc68/</guid><description>
The Elastic Stack (formerly the ELK Stack) is composed of 4 core open source tools that create the stack, these tools combined allow for data to be taken from any source securely and used to search, analyse and visualise in real time. The core components consist of:
Elasticsearch is a distributed database that is easily searchable Logstash is a data ingestor that is used to filter and customise your data Kibana is the user interface that is used to analyse and visualise data in real time Beats are the simple, lightweight and quick data shipping programs What can Elastic Stack be used for?</description></item><item><title>ProjectModular - Automate Tasks with PowerShell</title><link>/posts/tech/projectmodular/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/tech/projectmodular/</guid><description>
What is ProjectModular? ProjectModular is a set of scripts written in PowerShell that was created to automate basic sysadmin/support jobs. It was designed to be a super user friendly experience for those who do not have a lot of PowerShell experience. To do that, most variables call back to a central file that can be edited after download.
Who can use ProjectModular? ProjectModular has been written so that anyone (with or without PowerShell knowledge) could pick it up, change a few fields and use it in their organisation to begin automating some tasks.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/archive/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Career</title><link>/career/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/career/</guid><description>
Experience Pure Security Associate Security Consultant (March 2020 - Present)
Multigate Medical Products Security Administrator (September 2018 - March 2020)
IT Support Officer (July 2017 - September 2018)
Gilroy Catholic College Information Technology Support (December 2014 - December 2016)
Education Offensive Security Certified Professional (June 2020)
Certificate IV, Information Technology Networking (December 2016)
Projects Project Modular
A set of PowerShell tools created to assist in automating basic system administrator tasks.</description></item><item><title>Gilroy Catholic College</title><link>/posts/career/gilroy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/career/gilroy/</guid><description>
Information Technology Support Over the period of two years I was one of three IT support staff at Gilroy College whilst I was completing a Certificate IV in Information Technology Networking at TAFE. My role was mainly focused on providing support to over 1,200 staff and students on site. Support ranged from simple computer issues and printer problems to server and system updates.
Achievements Trainee of the Year 2016
JIRA Helpdesk System</description></item><item><title>Multigate Medical Products</title><link>/posts/career/multigate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/career/multigate/</guid><description>
IT Support Officer My main role was to provide IT support to the 100+ onsite staff and 40+ offsite staff for both Multigate and their sister company MDevices. Although a lot of my role was general support issues, there was a lot of flexibility for me to complete tasks that a System Administrator would otherwise complete.
Security Administrator After being in my role for over a year I was promoted to my new role which consisted of my previous work along with some additional security responsibilities (firewall configuration, Active Directory permissions, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>