<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blueteam on 0ldMate&#39;s Page</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/tags/blueteam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blueteam on 0ldMate&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/blueteam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack - How you can use it to assist your Incident Response</title>
      <link>/posts/tech/elastic-stack-how-you-can-use-it-to-assist-your-in-f31f7a3f9a8a42c0b860523f4b79cc68/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tech/elastic-stack-how-you-can-use-it-to-assist-your-in-f31f7a3f9a8a42c0b860523f4b79cc68/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          The Elastic Stack (formerly the ELK Stack) is composed of 4 core open source tools that create the stack, these tools combined allow for data to be taken from any source securely and used to search, analyse and visualise in real time. The core components consist of:
 Elasticsearch is a distributed database that is easily searchable Logstash is a data ingestor that is used to filter and customise your data Kibana is the user interface that is used to analyse and visualise data in real time Beats are the simple, lightweight and quick data shipping programs  What can Elastic Stack be used for?
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProjectModular - Automate Tasks with PowerShell</title>
      <link>/posts/tech/projectmodular/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tech/projectmodular/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          What is ProjectModular? ProjectModular is a set of scripts written in PowerShell that was created to automate basic sysadmin/support jobs. It was designed to be a super user friendly experience for those who do not have a lot of PowerShell experience. To do that, most variables call back to a central file that can be edited after download.
Who can use ProjectModular? ProjectModular has been written so that anyone (with or without PowerShell knowledge) could pick it up, change a few fields and use it in their organisation to begin automating some tasks.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>